We are identical twins...
but we are poles apart.
He lags behind
where as I, zoom ahead.
Charlie! That..
He stammers and...
I pronounce S as F.
HOW?
On his death bed,
my father said "Charlie, always remember...
...life is a bitch!.
And the only way to deal with life
Life is to be
The path we choose doesn't screw our life...
There are two ways to earn a quick buck!
A shortcut...
and a shorter shortcut!
Get him!
I took the shortcut...,
yet my dreams got screwed.
Big time!
Blue thunder.
My dreams..
My sweet little dreams.
My life and my world.
My booking window.
In reality...
I'm just a small time gangster.
Our gang fixes derbies.
Come on! Come on!
People usually wager on
the favourite to win
while we bet on it to lose.
Blue Thunder was the favourite,
in yesterday's race...
and the race was fixed.
I had bet all my savings rupees one lakh...
on that horse.
But the jockey double crossed us.
This shortcut cost me dearly.
Our booking company lost
it's reputation and fortune.
The company is run by
three Bengali brothers.
This is Mujeeb and that's Shumon.
Mikhail, the third Bengali brother.
How're you?
- The same as you!
My buddy,
dearer than my own brother.
A kid at heart but
a maniac in the head.
Indian National Small Arms System.
In short INSAS.
The heroine of the Kargil war...
purely homebred.
A distant cousin of the AKA'! .
Weight: 6.37 kgs.
Range: 700 meters.
Feed: 30 round - plastic box magazine.
How many can it kill in one round?
Sir, you'll lose count,
but the bullets will carry on.
Some people change with time...
and how the times change for some.
Arsehole...
money can be quite the devil.
You had to pull the reins here.
Double cross Burgess!
Double cross!
Shumon!
- Yes...
The viewfinder is screwed.
Brother says the viewfinder is off mark.
Not possible, sir.
Big brother never lies!
Please don't do this.
- Do what?
You screw us all over that's cool, huh?
The sky disappeared and
my balls vanished from my boxers!
You know how much we lost?
Charlie, they will kill me.
And we will worship you!
Stop crying, you rascal!
Brother says if he
aims at Burgess' head
the bullet will hit the clock instead.
Not the clock... the lamp.
The lamp!
Please forgive me!
I'm the one who is screwed here.
Royally screwed!
If I start crying,
you'll drown in my tears.
I want his name!
Francis!
Franfif?
You're growing senile day by day.
You've absolutely lost it!
What if I were shot?
My cute little darling...
Stop flashing your pearlies!
He almost crapped in his pants!
Even you would've crapped!
Such a coward!
You really thought he would shoot you?
You are shit scared!
What did you say?
Growing senile day by day?
You're absolutely right!
All three are nuts!
Every brother in the world is crazy.
Just like mine!
Here comes the Love Bee
Whiplash him, Fatak!
Here he comes, humming
Here comes the Love Bee...
Here he comes...humming
Bumbling through the lanes
Hasn't found anyone worth desiring,
no, not yet
Whiplash him, Fatak!
He deals off his friends
Look at the dandy, the way he struts
Full of swagger and all
Whiplash him, Fatak!
Hurl him on the ground
Dare you count on him as a friend
The rogue aimlessly tramps the streets
This leech will always feed on you
He may go but will return soon
In every defiled droplet of blood
To nibble your life away
Look, look he returns
He returns this illicit child of the night
Whiplash him, Fatak!
Here comes the Love Bee...
Here he comes...humming
Here he comes..humming
Bumbling through the lanes
Hasn't found anyone worth desiring,
no, not yet
Here comes the Love Bee...
Here he comes...humming
This love is not easy
The fear of AIDS hovers around
Wear your oars
This river is made of fire
Be careful, lest your boat capsizes
Be careful, lest the Love Bee stings
Jeetu, where's Guddu?
Where's Guddu?
Guddu!
We need to talk...
Listen!
Guddu listen to me...
The boat capsized...
Capsized!
Let's do another test?
This was the third.
When did you go for the other two?
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't want to stress you out
- And now?
Now where's your s... s...
Sincerity?
Safety?
What is it?
- Science!
Home science? Huh?
It was right here...
Kama Sutra condoms, a full packet.
Forget about it.
I'm a topper in home science.
Home science?
What do you mean?
I mean...
there's no danger today.
I don't like anything between us.
Nothing!
Glad the damn thing is lost.
Let me take one last look...
it's got to be here.
- You're such a dork.
Let it be!
Do you know the distance
it creates between us?
Like I'm in New York and...
you're in New... New...
New Jersey?
New
- New Zealand?
New Delhi?
New... New...
New Bombay.
Not Bombay... Mumbai.
You love Mumbai?
Yes, doctor.
I'll call you later.
He says it will be done in a day.
I can be back in four hours...
same day.
Fix an appointment for tomorrow?
Please say something.
- Do as you like.
I won't be part of this murder.
What do you mean?
Oh my!
Got it!
My single piece.
We'll sail through!
I'm ready to be a mother...
But I'm not ready to become a father!
Please understand, my dear!
We don't have enough
to support each other.
How do we support a child?
Things will fall into place.
This is our destiny.
Our destiny is screwed.
Big time!
I can't get married right now.
Period!
Why not?
All yours.
My life... my plan... my future...
Marriage in 2014...
and honeymoon in 2009!
Bravo Mr Sharma.
Bravo!
You wanted it!
And you didn't?
No!
So I must have raped you then!?
And all those promises...
was it the booze?
Baby! It feels as though
I've known you for ages.
Please, listen...
I'll take up a job.
But I still can't marry you now.
I mean...
I mean... I mean...
What do you mean?
You don't want an abortion
nor want to marry.
What do you want?
I just want to die.
Fine! Go die!
Please Guddu... please...
I can't see you die.
I am not committing suicide.
I know but if
we don't get married soon...
you'll be killed for sure.
Listen... my full name is...
Sweety Shekhar Bhope.
I'm Sunil "Chopper" Bhope's sister.
Guddu...
Bho... Bho...
De!
Hail Maharashtra!
We sent someone to check.
She hasn't been to college
for a month.
Uncle
Been bunking!
Who's the boy?
- I want a chocolate!
Some "Guddu".
Address?
- Navi Mumbai
Uncle, I want a chocolate...
- Shut up!
Miser!
Get the cars out!
- Chief, listen to me...
We've got that interview
lined up for today.
It's taken us 15 years
to clear our name.
Today is your interview.
Live on television.
Just relax and...
let me handle this.
Trust me on this one.
Look at that
your blood sugar level
is down to 110.
We'll slice the boy
and serve him for dessert.
Hail Maharashtra!
It's not my fault that
he is my brother!
The fault is that you lied to me.
Why?
Don't you trust me?
Have some water.
Add some poison as well.
Then you will die.
At least I'll be out of your way.
That's the point!
I'm as good as dead without you!
Then we will float around as ghosts!
And your brother can't stop
ghosts from getting married.
There's a slight problem though.
Can ghosts have kids?
So... when do we take the plunge?
Today
HOW...
Hello... hello...
Can you hear me?
Yes, go ahead.
Yes, it's fixed.
Eight o'clock? Hold on...
ls eight o'clock fine?
For what?
- Our wedding...
Eii... eight...
- Yeah... eight o'clock.
Today?
No... in 2014!
Yes... eight o'clock sounds good.
When days are dogs
Life's a bitch!
Once there was
some integrity in this business...
but not anymore!
And now, my mind is occupied
with just one name...
Franfif!
I found Franfif...
Awesome!
He is staying right here.
Room 716.
He fixing a race right now!
Alright, I'll inform big bro.
Leave right now.
And when I say leave,
you better leave.
Let's go.
Come on...
We leave this way.
But destiny lies that way.
Mr Narang?
From today I'm Tashi's pet...
Where are you?
- Where do you think?
Got the guitar?
Come over to the Madh Island bungalow.
Cool!
Afghanibhai, is Tashi around?
Why?
The airline guys are offering a deal.
Hold on...
TashL"
the flight purser at the hotel
has something to say.
Go on...
Tashi, he wants to say that
he is now your pet dog.
I have far too many dogs.
What the hell!
Where are the Africans?
- In Goa.
Call them.
Tell them the guitar
has been arranged for.
They will pick you up
for the race course tomorrow.
The Bengal is are
sniffing you down like rabid dogs.
Anything you need,
will be delivered to your room.
But I'll need a wakeup call.
I'll be fast sleep,
counting horses instead of sheep.
How the times have changed...
You got your gun on you?
- Yes.
Go back and give it to him.
- Okay.
Why take a chance?
Meet me in the parking lot.
- Okay.
I want my money back.
One lakh.
He only has pennies.
Look for his ATM card.
You want to
become a bookie, don't you?
I'll get it done in a jiffy.
Let's just give the gun and leave.
Packing the whole hotel in or what?
Help! Room Service!
This way! Come along!
Shut it!
What was that?
Stop the car!
Damn it! Stop the car!
They're getting away!
- Stop them!
Damn! Cops! We are screwed!
- Don't freak out!
Steve... pass my shades!
My shades!
We'll make it, don't worry.
That was close.
You knew that guy?
- Nope!
Then why did you salute him?
Because he saluted me!
Why would a cop salute you?
What!?
Hey junkies...
What the hell?
Sir, seems like it was a major deal.
And it went wrong!
On the floor where
we found the dead bodies...
the security cameras were damaged
What are you doing?
Did you have prior information?
We were expecting someone but...
did you check
the other security cameras?
No, it's being done.
- Then do it!
You want to talk?
Okay... move it!
Where the hell are you?
- Afghanibhai...
There's a problem.
We were leaving the hotel
but got stuck
in a crossfire between two gangs.
You are still in Panvel?
- Yes and the DCP is here as well.
It's difficult to leave.
- Like I care!
We fixed the delivery
as per your time.
I get it but...
please try and understand.
Try telling this to Tashi.
I'll hand him the phone.
Look, security is tight
and sniffer dogs are around.
What's more important?
Guitar's safety or scheduled delivery?
Fine! Commit a final time!
Problem, safety and all that.
Tell me!
Eight...
- Eight o'clock.
Tomorrow morning?
Why don't you come over here
and collect it yourself.
OK!
But eight means eight, clear?
Loud and clear!
By the Way"-
the guitar is safe?
- Should I play a tune?
See you tomorrow.
- Tune?
Where is Sweety?
- Tear this place apart!
Tell me or I'll break your head!
He is Charlie's brother.
Charlie who?
That gambler from the train yard!
Chief, there is good news
and bad news.
He seems to be a nice guy.
Works for an NGO besides...
Bad! Give me the bad!
They genuinely love each other!
They're getting married.
I could stop it if you say so.
But they do look like...
they're made for each other.
I'll get your mom hooked up with him!
Get me Sweety on the phone!
- Yes, Chief!
As soon as I get there.
Damn it! What's going on!
From the frying pan into the fire...
and back into the frying pan!
Forget it.
Don't even think about it!
Just get away!
Charlie...
The shortcut
or the shorter fhortcut!
But - But what?
Don't forget!
The path you choose doesn't screw your life...
what screws you is...
the one you leave behind!
Greetings, everyone.
Please remain seated.
Sweety dear...
Where have you been?
Been looking all over for you.
Greetings!
I am your brother-in-law.
I consider myself an Indian first
and then a Marathi.
But what annoys me is that
my house guest...
who shares my food...
shares my wages...
drinks my milk...
saves the butter
for his own toast.
How is that fair?
Now even...
- Cut!
Brother...
Why are you doing this to me?
I wanted to make
your wedding a grand affair.
Why did you hurt me?
You wanted me to
marry that builder's son...- So?
And who is this boy?
What is his name?
Tell me...
Sanjay...
Sanjay?
Give me his full name!
Sanjay Kumar Sharma,
son of Kishan Kumar Sharma...
bows to the 25 crores
Gods and Goddesses...
Hang on!
Come again. What is his name?
Sanjay Kumar Sharma.
Sanjay Kumar Sharma?
Where are you from?
Barabanki.
Barabanki? U.P.?
Holy crap!
Give me the phone.
Just give the damn phone!
Chief... we are screwed!
He is a bloody migrant, from U.P.!
We've identified the dead bodies.
They belong to the K D Narang gang.
But the boy in the camera footage
Don't know how he is connected to this.
Investigations are still on.
This way, Sir...
Play it.
Rewind... slower...
Get him! Closer.
Beat the crap out of him.
Bloody migrant!
Let him go...
I would've killed you right now...
You sons of bitches!
Leave him...
- Sweety get away!
Guddu, get up!
Dare not touch him!
Don't you get it?
Your chief is ready to
trade his sister for votes.
I don't want to marry
that builder's wretched son.
At least you should've supported me.
I'll speak to chief...
- Back off!
You...
Get the car keys.
Move it!
To hell with the polictics...
that builder's son
To hell with brother!
I'll talk to him...
Douse the fire!
They're getting away!
Take it easy. Don't be a fool.
He is part of the family.
I'm here to do business!
Watch what you say! - He's right.
Awesome! Killer stuff!
Where did you get it from?
How much do I get?
How much do you want?
Ten!
You got it!
Lakhs!
For one packet?
A hundred packets!
Come again?
A hundred!
You created a ruckus
at the hotel, didn't you?
I told you to leave immediately.
Leaving wouldn't have helped.
Opportunity came knocking
and I grabbed it!
Lady luck smiled on me!
A hundred packets of...
cocaine!
And they belong to?
Us!
What will you do with ten lakhs?
I'll become a bookie.
You bloody scoundrel!
Open your mouth
- ha ha ha!- No...
With a hundred packets
we'll make enough...
to own the entire racecourse!
And then!
Spain... France... Miami... Copacabana...
Psychedelic Trance! Dude!
Come on!
Let's rock!
Shake the booty!
Come, let's wring our hearts
Smash the pot of the night
Come, let's pry out some good luck
Let's break into the vault
Tiny sprouts of leafy cress,
and oil from oilman's press
Life is nothing but money's play
Let's have a face-off on the roads tonight
Step out
Life is a one way
All you get is one chance
Nothing ahead but thin air
And the romance lasts till the breath does
This is what they say
This is what we hear
Whosoever surges ahead
Never does come back
Come, let's wring tomorrow
Smash the pot of the night
Come, let's pry out some good luck
Tonight, let's break into the vault
Tiny sprouts of leafy cress,
and oil from oilman's press
Life is nothing but money's play
Let's have a face-off on the roads tonight
Looks like an amateur crook.
The revolver, money,
everything is still here.
Is anything missing?
This time lets play such a game
That the ocean walks over the bridge
Then whether you walk on the bridge or I
The city will stay under our feet
Somewhere the news are grave
Somewhere there are just graves
Hush! Let's not wake up the dead
Come, let's wring our hearts
Smash the pot of the night
Come, let's pry out some good luck
Let's break into the vault
Dhan te nan...!
I've got the tickets and passports.
Go and freshen up soon!
I'll get the first-aid box.
Hurry up!
We will miss the flight!
What is wrong with you?
What's wrong?
I almost flunked in the sixth grade.
What?
We sat on the same bench.
Both of us.
Who both?
Sabiha and I.
Sabiha Laeek Ahmed.
I was in love with her.
She loved hearings...
stories from me.
Champak, Nandan...
Bela Bahadur... comics.
Then one day I realised...
it wasn't the stories she loved.
It was my fumbling that made her laugh.
Once I caught her...
imitating me.
Gh... gh... Q“-.
That's when I realised that...
not only do I stammer...
but I'm a duffer too.
Listen...
you can narrate
the rest at the a... a... aiirp
Just remembered, didn't you?
The stammer?
What happened back there
at the war zone?
Forgot your cues?
Why pull this farce on me?
How many more lies?
Every lie had an honest intention...
- Another lie!
We'll miss our flight...
- What's the hurry?
Let's get to know each other better.
I'm your wife.
That's a lie!
You are Bhope's sister!
I'm carrying your child.
- Really?
Are you sure it's mine?
I'll kill you!
Cheater!
You'll die soon!
As if you'll live forever!
How about I slit your throat?
Do you know the stuff's worth?
Ten crores!
Groves'?
The stuff is worth ten croresl?
Yeah man! Ten crores!
At least.
Go on darling...
get the stuff, quick!
I'll set up some deals till then.
Now get 905719!
Ten! Arsehole!
I'll be back in five.
- Make it quick!
Hello... big bro...
Staying alive...
Stop behaving like the bride
and lend me a hand!
Please come in Mr Sharma.
Sorry... we barged in unannounced!
We waited outside for a while...
but we were hungry...
so we came in,
hoping to find something to eat.
Nothing beats fresh burgers
on a rainy day!
Please have a seat.
To tell you the truth...
we are looking for the groom.
Excuse me?
Guddu.
How many brothers are you?
Two.
If you were three
would you parade me naked?
What do you do?
Builder, chief...
Body builder!
Wow Mr. Sharma...
Well built, I'm impressed!
Do you have a sister?
I have one.
Your brother screwed her.
And now they're getting married.
Weren't you invited?
Doesn't matter now...
neither was I.
Where can we find him?
It's been three years since...
I saw his shitty face.
I swear!
Right now...
I need to take care of
something important.
I'll call you once I hear from him.
Can I have your fell number?
What's he saying?
Which number?
Fell.
Mobile.
Do you lisp?
Not really...
I pronounce S as F...
If not as F,
will you pronounce it as L?
What about your brother?
Does he lisp as well?
He stammers.
One lisps and...
the other stammers!
Where is he?
He is inside.
But there is some confusion.
This way.
I'm tired of repeating myself.
You can't keep me here,
without a warrant.
This is against the law.
- Against the law?
We'll take it from here. Thank you.
- Sir?
Didn't you hear him?
Get moving. Now!
The law does not p... p...
permit this?
So you're the lawmaker now?
There has been a misunders... s... s...
Here... have a seat.
Sit down!
'I!' 'II!
I'm not who you th... th...
think I am.
And who is that?
- I'm not Ch... Ch... Ch...
Chimpanzee!
That's what we are!
Where's the guitar?
What gui... gui...
This is going to take all night!
Why don't you sing something?
Sing?
What?
- A song!
Can't get it started.
Water might have seeped in.
- Take your time!
Have you ever met him?
No.
- Good for you. You've been lucky!
He brings misfortune!
There could be no worse omen...
than to see his shitty face.
You mentioned him
and my phone conked out!
What's going on here?
I'm out in the rain cracking deals
and you're chilling in here!
Mikhail, I'll be out with you in a bit!
Hold on...
Something smells fishy!
Hey you...
Are you giving
my brother a hard time?
Chief, hold on to your pants!
The third brother is here!
You don't get it, Mikhail.
He is Chief Bhope.
Chief... who?
- Chief Bhope! You should leave.- So?
I'm Chief Tope!
Chief Tope, Chief Bhope,
Chief Chief Bhope Tope...
Chief Bhope Chief Tope...
Bhope Tope
Chief Tope Bhope Chief...
Bhope Tope Boom!
The stuff has been sold.
So kindly leave.
Or I'll pluck out
your chilli and two nuts
and pawn them at the traffic signal.
Got it!?
You still don't get it!
- No, no... hold it!
He gets everything!
Chief Tope, this way...
- Watch it!
You're a great man.
I bow down to...
the dude of this century!
Why don't you have a seat, please...
A burger... quick!
We are two brothers...
Identical twins...
thus we look the same.
Brother...
you are great!
Doesn't stammer while singing.
Go on...
Listen, he...
Keep singing-
He's an arsehole...
A bloody scoundrel...
He does the deed...
And I pay the price...
Always been so.
If each of your fingers...
is worth a crore...
Then five fingers
would be worth how much more?
How much?
Five- Both?
- T... T... Ten...
With your ten excuses
you stole my heart away...
Arsehole!
Kiddo!
There is powder worth
ten crores in the guitar.
If we don't get it back,
we are dead.
And so are you!
That's my br... br... brother...
Cha... Charlie's ph... ph... photo.
I'm Gu... Guddu.
Here's your burger!
What deal were you talking about?
None of your business!
Alright...
at least tell me its worth.
I haven't plucked your stuff yet.
How can I sell it?
Will this chilli do?
Or should I pluck the real one out?
The phone is working now.
Mikhail... wait outside... I'll join you.
Why are you winking at me?
Why should I leave?
They should be the ones leaving.
It's time you and
your circus troupe left.
Circus troupe?
Or I may have to stuff the chilli.
As in?
- You know what we do...
when a horse refuses to run?
We stuff the chilli up the horse!
How it takes off then
Tik tok tik tok tik tok tik tok.
Later on...
to catch up with it...
the jockey sticks two up his own!
- Two?
Zip zap zip zap Zip Zap-
Our way of dealing with...
laggards is a little different.
We don't try to make them run.
We just blow them off.
Mikhail...
Call him! Your cell...
Call now!
I know he's inside,
please let me meet him.
It's not allowed.
The interrogation is still on.
Why not?
What's his crime?
We'll drop him home
after the interrogation.
I'll report this to the media!
Remember the Rehman-ur-Rehman case?
- Very well.
The Police Commissioner got transferred!
- Like I care!
I'll make sure you lose your job!
Go and do as you wish!
I'm not going anywhere!
Arrest me as well.
Patil!
Send Inspector Manju over here.
Fine, we'll arrest you as well.
My husband is in there,
let me go...
Stop her!
- Guddu... Guddu...
I swear I don't have it.
- Where is it?
Don't you understand?
- Please listen...
What is this ruckus?
Prateek, what's going on?
She forced her way in.
I beg you to let him go.
She is his wife...
- Whose wife?
Please leave my foot.
Calm her down!
Heisinnocent
- Okay...
Sir, please...
- Alright!
Yes, Charlie is with me.
She's my sister.
Treat her with respect!
Put Shinde on the line...
Shinde...
Prateek...
Go and prepare the Nagpal Case report.
But Sir...
- Get going!
We are in a war like situation.
That too,
it's a biological war.
And your brother is
on the enemie's side.
The cocaine belongs to the government,
belongs to us...
and he has stolen that.
So sad, isn't it?
Mr Sharma, by this time tomorrow
you'll be in Barabanki.
Mumbai police! Everyone out!
This way please.
Please alight the train.
Please cooperate with us.
Out... everyone.
Ma'am, you too... soon.
Relax...
This is for you.
Now you'll be
free of Bhope's clutches.
Please have a seat.
Finally!
Please eat something!
You haven't eaten a thing.
Don't vent your anger
on this poor burger.
You wouldn't even look at me.
Do you remember?
If I didn't pretend to stammer...
you wouldn't have spoken to me.
Stuck in your own shell...
aloof from the rest of the world.
I left everything behind for you.
And all those things you said to me!
Please forgive me.
If it weren't for you...
I wouldn't have gone for
the speech therapy.
See
I don't get stuck on S anymore.
I agree I'm a psy... psy...
Psycho!
No, a psycho's husband!
Move it... clear it...
Damn it! Answer the phone!
Where are you?
We talked about five people,
I can see six.
So shoot one down
but where are you?
Behind you.
The exchange will happen
in our compartment...
at the next stop.
Where's Charlie?
- Charlie...
Don't do this.
Killing me won't help you.
- And keeping you alive will?
I'll give you one crore rupees.
- That's it?
One and half.
Two... two and half...
You lisping jerk!
Had you told me about
your deal then...
I could've let you go.
Now you can screw yourself.
If you ever talk to me
like that again...
I'll kill myself. I swear!
Never again!
I swear on our little girl.
Not a girl, a boy!
Girl...
- Boy...
_ NA Qirl!
o: a
Rise and shine...
Are we there already?
- Yes, this is your last stop. Come on.
What's the problem?
Five crores... five!
Brother...
Six crores!
I'll be damned!
It's Thomson and Thompson!
Hey Ram and Shyam?
If anybody tries to act smart,
I'll shoot her!
Put the gun down.
- Don't shoot her.
Save me.
- Leave my sister!
I'll kill you!
Stop the train.
- Pull the chain! Now!
Do as I say.
- I won't spare you!
Pull the bloody chain!
Where is it?
Where have you hidden the guitar?
Spit it out!
We are stuck at Panvel
for the last two hours.
It's been pouring here.
I'm not lying, Afghanibhai.
All the roads are blocked!
Tell me when!
- It's not possible!
It could take hours.
We haven't slept at all.
Shall I sing a lullaby?
Tell me, should I?
Tell him to call
on reaching the jetty.
Listen carefully...
call as soon as you reach Mumbai.
One...
two...
Three... four... five... six...
seven... eight... nine... ten!
Shoot! Go on shoot!
Can't do it, can you?
Our lives are
trapped in that guitar case.
Once you lay your hands on it...
you'll shoot me without blinking!
Lower your gun and...
call your boss.
Now!
You want to talk to the boss, huh?
The car is stuck,
can you take a look?
Call the boss!
It's a bloody movie or what!
Come back now... little more.
Move forward now.
Accelerate...
- Tell me when.
Put it in reverse now.
Keep going-
What happened?
You're shot!
How did this happen?
The car skidded... I didn't see...
I'm sorry...
Let's get you up...
please...
try getting up...
No!
Take grandma inside...
and Sweety as well.
No, I won't.
I'll sit right here...
with my husband.
Shameless fool!
Putting me through this hell.
What are you staring at?
Lower your eyes.
Is this your culture?
To lure innocent girls
and screw them!
When did you arrive here?
Here in Bombay?
- Mumbai!
I was born here.
But father arrived in B...
Bombay in 1984.
- Mumbai!
It was called Bombay back then.
Bastard! It was Mumbai then
and it is Mumbai now!
You bloody migrants...
are chewing the city
hollow like termites!
The city is bursting at it's seams...
and you people swarm in like flies!
To rob our share of the pie.
My father used to say that...
we are like sugar added to milk.
If we leave,
the milk won't lessen but...
will turn bland.
How thoughtful!
The chief has diabetes.
What do we do with him?
Listen...
I understand your love for each other.
I got a vibe in the train.
But if my sister marries a migrant...
I'll be crucified!
My grave will be dug.
Not only will I lose my reputation...
but my election fund as well.
The builder is paying me to
get his son and Sweety married.
Five crores!
Can you imagine how much that is?
There is powder worth
ten crores in the guitar.
How much?
Five whopping crores!
If I give you ten...
will you sell her to me?
Ten crores!
I can take it all if I want.
But all I want is ten lakhs.
What is your name?
Anything you want to call me!
Do you know who I am?
No... but I know you're badly screwed!
You don't have a choice.
I'll dig you out from your grave.
Have mercy!
You can have it all!
Shut the crap!
Useless dolts!
As soon as I'm away...
you guys start jerking off!
Tell me!
Chief, we were...
Chief, "chief"...
stop barking!
Grandma has given the nod!
Brother-in-law, can you believe it?
It wasn't easy getting her around.
She can be quite fickle...
so we've got to act quickly!
Go get the guitar!
We'll take care of the wedding.
Start the arrangements right away...
contact the caterer...
and go tell grandma
to make sweets.
We're having a feast tonight.
Why haven't you left?
You should get going...
What about the election now?
What about it?
I'll join the party that backs your lot.
Brother-in-law...
politics is a business.
Power and family.
That's all that matters!
Done digging my grave?
Reporting from inside the coffin.
You got your ten lakhs.
Deal. Take down the address.
I've sent the address and plan.
With whom?
Police.
Should be on their way.
Look at that!
Chief Tope...
sleeping like a baby!
Let's find the guitar.
Daddy...
Found the guitar?
- Still searching.
Beware! The lisper is with the cops!
They'll come around sniffing.
- Alright.
As soon as you find the stuff
shoot him off.- Sure.
What if we don't find it?
Then get your mom hooked up with him!
Why drag my poor mom into this?
Hail Maharashtra!
- Hail Maharashtra!
What are you doing here?
Listening.
Listening to what?
How about a chocolate?
- No, I want a car!
My god! A car?
Keep this!
This won't even get me a bicycle.
Is this good enough?
Remember, you heard nothing!
Now scram!
You shitface!
You aren't dead yet?
Now what do you want?
- You're alright?
The police let you go?
Disappointed to see me alive?
Arsehole!
You almost sacrificed me for the girl.
We got married last night.
Now you want a wedding gift?
I need a loan.
Did the sun rise from the west today?
Will my filthy money be...
good for you?
I don't want money...
I want the guitar case.
Come again?
I'll gouge your eyes out,
if you even look at it.
Sweety's life depends on it.
- How sweet!
She's pregnant.
- I'm not responsible.
I will repay every Penny-
Wasn't I d... dead for you?
Arsehole!
Remember, what you
swore on dad's pyre?
I don't want to see
your f... f... face ever again.
Stop blaming yourself!
Bury the ghosts of the past.
Forgive yourself.
Whose ghosts?
Forgive myself for what?
Even if you
got the money on time...
dad would've killed himself.
Neither of us are responsible
for his death.
But we are responsible
for our own lives.
Let me go or it'll be too late.
Guddu!
Life is offering you a second chance.
Don't walk away from the right path.
I swear I'll shoot.
There was a time...
when we were inseparable.
Daddy...
We were so happy-
He was both
a mother and father to us.
He was our hero.
A thief, he wasn't.
What made him steal the watch...
and for whom...
was beyond our understanding.
Five thousand, nothing less.
I've spoken with the boss.
Go get it.
We'll let your father go.
They've asked for five, I have three.
How?
- Scholarship...
Where is it?
- The wa... wa...
The watch tower?
- Yes.
Stay with father,
I'll be back with five.
By the time
I returned with the money...
father had committed suicide.
And with his death...
we were brothers no more.
Open your mouth... ha.. ha.. ha...!
Daddy...
This is the voice-mail box of Inspector Lele.
Leave a message after the beep.
Hail Maharashtra, Hail India!
Mr Charlie...
This is Inspector Lele...
We've arranged for your ten lakhs.
Sir, where do we meet?
Sir, please call back when free.
Now can you call for a doctor?
He'll bleed to death.
- Kiddo...
' Sir?
Call!
And if he doesn't answer...
shoot yourself!
Kiddo...
We're screwed!
For real!
Enough is enough!
- What do you mean?
If you want you can call me,
when the stuff comes.
I'll be in India somewhere.
Tashi has everything under control.
You've got to trust me on this.
He is messing with us.
Can't you see?
Cajetan, if you walk through that door,
I'll shoot you.
This is the voice-mail box of Inspector Lele.
Leave a message after the beep.
Hail Maharashtra, Hail India!
Please...
I have given my blood for the diamonds.
Get it?
Forgive me, brother.
Now do I get another chance?
The department suspects these two...
are working for the underworld.
What can Life do
Now that I have fallen into its lot
I have sapped its spirit
Gnawed at its flesh
With my incessant complaints
Day in and day out
My desires are mean
Mean are my dreams too
A little rapport
I had struck with the heart
That monsieur too
turned out to be mean
What can Life do
Now that I have fallen into its lot
I have sapped its spirit
Gnawed at its flesh
With my incessant complaints
Day in and day out
Sweety, have you lost it!
Guddu must be on his way back
put the gun down.
You're a swine!
I know what you told
Ganesh over the phone.
You're misunderstanding me.
I swear!
Go on...
90 get her!
We'll be able to hear each other.
Don't do anything,
until I instruct you.
Remember...
we have to catch Bhope red handed.
Wear this.
I'll kill you...
- Me? You'll kill me?
Go ahead!
You were this little
when mother passed away.
Just like a small kitten.
Shoot me and then you can leave.
Let's see what you've got.
Guddu... - Now go... go on...
So...
should I blow up his skull?
Lower the gun!
Sun“ Shekhar Bhope.
Bhope...
Afghani, stay with the Africans.
Grandpa! Where is Bhope?
He's in the courtyard.
Screwed... big time!
Lower the gun... please!
Why don't you tell her
to lower the gun?
Let me be.
- He's saying...
G... gun... lower the gun.
Hand over the guitar, quickly!
The stuff...
- Screw the stuff!
Talk some sense into her!
Lower the g... gun...
I'm absolutely fine.
Bhope...
You'll shoot me?
You actually shot me?
How dare you?
Get lost!
Chief... here...
chief
Relax, Bhope... take it easy.
Who the hell are you?
Even we've got guns.
Big ones!
But who wants a war?
I'm not America.
This is Maharashtra!
Who the hell are you?
- Me? I'm Tashi.
Tashi, the Great!
I don't believe this!
You're alive.
Move the guitar. Move it!
Tashi! A tiger in a mousetrap!
Call headquarters for reinforcements.
- Copy Sir.
Headquarter come in,
this is Tigerhead.
Team One is moving in.
We need back-up.
Guddu, we're coming in, don't panic.
It's going to be okay.
Granted you have the stuff.
How do you plan to sell it and to whom?
Ultimately the guitar
will come back to me!
How much for your charity fund?
Ten crores! Cash!
In Dollars or Euros?
You freaking dirty rat!
This is the Anti-Narcotics Cell
of the Mumbai police!
Surrender your guns!
This is the Anti-Narcotics Cell
of the Mumbai police!
Surrender your guns!
Don't move or I'll shoot!
I'll kill your spy.
If he is hurt,
nobody will be spared.
Surrender yourselves!
You have no option.
There is an option.
Hey Pele...
Tell him your plan!
I'm Lele, not Pele!
- Whatever!
Tell the Inspector, he gets 33%.
Prateek... it's me Inspector Lele.
What you doing up there?
Come down.
The stuff is worth ten crores.
3,33,33,333.33... all ours!
All yours!
- And there's no Lobo to share it with.
Come down.
Hold your fire.
What the hell is this?
- Shut up, Cajetan!
Tashi, he is right!
Shut the hell up... shut up!
Last and final,
60, 20, 20.
Or you can shoot!
- Shoot?
Go on shoot!
Shoot and I'll burn the stuff!
Hold your fire!
Charlie boy... great job!
Fourth partner!
25% each!
Now come down.
Hey... knucklehead!
I didn't risk it all
for the money.
I did it for this stupid Romeo!
He doesn't know this world is a bitch
and how rotten you dogs really are!
Let him go!
Her as well.
Take your Juliet along and run!
And you?
You'll kill me
with all your love!
Get moving!
At least for the baby's sake.
Guddu, move it!
Come down with the guitar!
Drop your gun!
This path that you bargained for
Will stay deserted
The noose of life
Does never snap
Who walk the edge of swords
will unfailingly get hurt
The noose snared around your neck
only tightens, does not snap
The color of blood
However sanguine
Fails to color life
The noose of life
Does never snap
Hail Maharashtra!
The sliver of time between
two breaths is too fine
Life is offering you
a second chance.
Don't walk away
from the right path.
My past sneaks into the future
and robs it off all hope
Rivers of blood
never find themselves an ocean
I told you, didn't I?
You'd have twins!
If you bet against me,
you'll always lose.
Now tell me...
whom do they look like?
How sweet!
One diamond adorns her finger
while she is a gem herself!
Sophia is her name and
she doesn't pronounce S as F!
I don't even have clothes to wear.
It's alright!
I prefer you without clothes.